jasonbondpicks.com 2019-07-08

# Privacy Policy | Jason Bond Picks

At JasonBondPicks.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by JasonBondPicks.com and how it is used.

#### Log Files:

Like many other Web sites, JasonBondPicks.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies:

JasonBondPicks.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

We comply with the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising as managed by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). You may opt out of receiving personalized ads from other companies that perform ad targeting services, including some that we may work with as Advertising Partners via the DAA website [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on JasonBondPicks.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to JasonBondPicks.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

#### Some of our advertising partners may use cookies on our site. Our advertising partners include but are not limited to:

  * Google Adsense
  * Commission Junction
  * Microsoft Bing

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on JasonBondPicks.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

JasonBondPicks.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. TopStockPicks.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

If you have any questions regarding our policies please feel free to contact us at the following URL:

#### SMS Marketing:

[Raging Bull](https://ragingbull.com/) provides an automated enrollment-based text messaging service via SMS. Customers may enroll at any time via our sign-up form, or when subscribing to the corresponding email list.

##### SMS Participation

Open only to residents of the United States of America and Canada. You must be 18 years or older in order to enroll in our SMS messaging services, or have the express permission of a parent/guardian.

By signing up for our SMS Messaging Services, you consent to receive our messages electronically. If you do not consent to the terms set forth herein, and/or do not wish to receive electronic messages, you must immediately cease using the services and [contact us](https://ragingbull.com/contact/).

Your agreement to the terms of service authorizes us to deliver advertising messages using an auto-dialer (as defined by the Federal Communications Commission); and you acknowledge that consent to these terms is not in any way required as a condition of making purchases from us or our affiliate companies.

You also agree that you are the account holder or have the express authorization to enroll..

Message frequency may vary based on carrier and account. Message and Data rates may apply. Please consult with your carrier for further information regarding rates applicable to your plan.

For our Canadian customers, standard Message and Data rates may apply. Please consult with your carrier for further information regarding rates applicable to your plan.

We are not responsible for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages as delivery is subject to effective transmission from you network operators.

##### SMS Opt-Out

At any time, you may opt-out of our SMS service by replying to any received message with the following word: **STOP**

If you have any questions or concerns, you may text **HELP** in response to any message. You can also reach out to our customer service representatives at [contact us](https://ragingbull.com/contact/).

##### SMS Data Collection

Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your cellphone number, your carrier’s name, the date, time and content of your messages and other information you provide to us as part of this service. We may use this information to contact you and to provide the services you request from us.

##### Children Under the Age of 13

This site and all services associated with it, including its mobile applications, SMS Services, and tools, are not marketed to, and do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from, children under the age of 13.
